Hello, everyone. I am a teacher from the Fashion and Fashion Design Department of Shanghai Shanda College.
What is different from the guests just now is that I learned about the experience of marketing from the perspective of product design.
I think it is more about how we can improve our experience, especially in the field of psychology, to express my thoughts on Clou.
What I think represents Clou is that Clou is a place where we can learn from each other.
Clou is a place where we can learn from each other.
For example, there are many young designers and school teachers in China.
I myself have developed some of the brand products for my own business, be it electronics, fashion or physical electronics.
I have also done various virtual-related courses in our team.
I have done a lot of virtual virtual classes.
In 2012, when I was in Korea, I found out that Clou was so popular in China.
发现了这样子一款软件
那个时候沟通还是属于都是在这种论坛里面去沟通的
那么我发现的原因其实是基于我自己的一个做科研的一个习惯
就是我自己在做科研的时候
我发现怎么可以这么蠢
就是我们还要一遍一遍的去fitting
一遍一遍的去做很多修改
怎么会没有这样的一个软件
然后我就去搜
我发现韩国出现了这样的一款软件
然后开始一点点跟着这个课程教程去学习
那么直到我自己毕业之后
我进入了院校
那么也不断的开始发现很多身边的同行都开始关注这个软件
那我觉得在我们这个时代其实有很多这种跨时代的产品
比如说像微信像阿里巴巴
那我觉得可口对于我们服装设计界而言
我觉得它是一个跨时代的产品
刚才有嘉宾提问说
觉得可口完全
它替代我们的一个真实的一个这样的一个时间是多久
我想跟大家说我们团队是做过一个地区性的调研的
包括跟很多的行业内的设计师
跟行业内的一些科研的人员跟教育者
就我们认为它替代的时间应该是五年
我这个数据是基于我们的一个真实调研的一个情况
也是因为基于这个数据
所以不仅仅我们的院校
像北京服装学院
像东华
像国美
其实全部都开设了这样的一个课程
所以我从一个教育者的这个角度
我们来看其实教育行业
我觉得可能有的时候会更敏感一些
因为我们的人才
我们是要在四年前就要去预感四年之后
可能学生他要面临什么样的一个市场
这样子的一个变化
所以我们要去制定相应的培养方案
那我们认为现在大部分的国内的一个教育体系里面的老师
其实都开始全面的推广客户的这样的一个软件了
这个不仅仅是对于我们自己而言
也是一些市场上实际的一些需求
所以如果有担心这个就是人才方面的问题
其实也可以联系我
因为像我们现在也有非常多的学生
在不同的这个公司里面去从事客户的这样子的一个虚拟设计
那么另外一方面呢
其实我们其实在做
整个的一个这个就是项目的时候呢
我们一开始最开始整个项目的进程
我们是做了很多创意的作品
我这里也给大家看一下我们的这个一些学生的作业
这个是我们现在所有的作品
我们都会要求它在院校里面的学生
就是把它做成虚拟的走秀展示
那大家可以看到
其实我们对于很多创意的作品
其实已经可以达到比较高的一个仿真度了
那不仅仅是在面料的一个垂感
包括还有图案的一些应用上面
大家可以看到就是刚才的这些
有一些作品里面呢
其实很多的款式它是比较复杂的
因为学校里面学生的毕业设计
它可能会用很多的
This is a basic judgment of the Chinese education talent in the market, that is, in the past, our education was more inclined to an artistic education.
In the 20th year of the reform and opening up, we began to try to do some brand education.
We believe that in the next 10 years, it will be a digital education.
Of course, this digitalization will not only remain in the digital design itself, but will also be combined with some VR and AR technologies.
Last year, we started to do a crowdfunding project with a well-known partner brand, Liyingfang.
We started to do a crowdfunding project with a well-known partner brand, Liyingfang.
So how to improve the experience?
In fact, we will go through different modes.
The first one is that we cooperate with this brand Linfa.
Then we will turn some student design styles into a virtualization.
Then they can choose.
This is the first step.
Then the second step, we will put this virtualized image,
especially on the same clothes.
As you know, it is very difficult to complete the same clothes for children from 3 to 5 years old.
Because it is very difficult for children to show off.
So at this time, the virtualization of Cloth has a very good effect.
We can present the details of the same clothes in the virtual show, including the virtual show.
The third one is the key to the experience.
Sometimes our children may draw some works.
Then these works he drew,
may want to put this work on the clothes to make a pattern.
This idea is actually based on the idea of some VIP customers of Linfa.
Then we will help him achieve it.
How to achieve it?
Maybe this child, he values ​​this style in the store.
Then scan his work in.
This pattern, children can make a customized feeling on their own clothes.
Then the third step is that we are now in the process of both sides.
One child wears a VR glasses.
He can experience the design he did in Cloth.
A detail of this kind of display.
Then this aspect is not only to promote the overall image of the brand.
Right?
The brand will be more technological.
At the same time, it will also contribute to a series of real-time customers.
Their consumption habits.
I can show you what we are doing.
You may see that this is a uniform of the clothes we are making.
That is, the children can put their own works.
Up here, an image is for a correction.
A alternative.
Then it can enhance the children's own styles.
As for the benefits of Grow, the previous guests have already talked about it in detail, so I don't think I need to go into detail.
But what I want to say is that we are not only concerned about the design of the software itself,
but we are also concerned about the digital assets.
There is a lot of research going on internationally, especially with the pandemic.
Many of us have started online meetings.
In fact, the latest project we are working on with some companies is a virtual image project.
What does it mean?
In the future, our clothes will not only have the role of physical clothes,
but in the future, we may sell virtual clothes.
For example, when you are in a meeting, your virtual image will also become the key to sales.
I think by that time,
whether we are active or passive, we must learn this software,
because we want to build such a virtual image.
It will become a virtual asset.
This is a small test of the project we are doing.
We put a picture of Grow's software in the test mirror,
so that customers can see the big picture made by them through the test mirror, especially children.
They may not be able to see the picture clearly on the computer,
but they can see it in the test mirror.
They can see some of the pictures they made on Grow's clothes.
The next step is to make a link with VR and AR.
Now we are also starting to connect with some small,
not small,
but small design brands.
I believe this model will be more and more accepted by many companies.
I can also introduce our own school here.
Shanda College is the only school in the country registered in the Ministry of Education.
The characteristic is that we are managed by the country,
unlike other schools in the Ministry of Education.
The second is that we have a very rich and flexible mechanism,
so we can work with many companies to develop some of these projects.
In our project development,
especially in the field of digitalization,
Grow is the foundation of all our projects.
Whether we want to do this experience or do VR in the future,
we all need to go through Grow's software to carry out a design of many styles.
This is also what most of our courses have been transformed into.
It has been transformed into digital design.
It may even be more important than our handmade production and handmade board.
This is my speech today.